In this segment we're going to cover a bet called Daily Double.
This is one of the more complicated bets that you can actually place at a racing establishment.
A Daily Double is basically an Exacta, with a really big twist.
You are betting on what's coming in first for the race in which that bet starts, and then the next race after that, on which number is going to come in first.
So, to explain that in a little better way.
Let's say that the Daily Double starts in race two and ends in race three.
So, for race two, we're picking what number we think is going to come in first, and that's the very first number we put in a Daily Double.
The second number is what's going to come in for the second race in the first position.
We can wheel this and we can also box it, but boxing gets really complicated on this bet and it's also really expensive.
If we were to wheel this, the first half of our wheel, if you remember back to our wheel, was a one.
And, we'd actually have to stop it after the second line because there's no third and fourth place that we're going to worry about.
And, in this wheel it's not first place and it's not second place, it's first race, second race, so again if we go back to our example: let's say we wanted to do one, two, three and four, five, six, we would do, ok, I want to do a Daily Double at this, I want to go to this track, do a one dollar daily Double.
I want to wheel the one, two, three, that's dog, horse or dog, one, two, or three coming in first place, on race two.
And, then four, five, six would be the wheel for the second race to come in first.
So, we want one, two, or three to come in first for race two, or four, fix and six to come in for race three.
It's not interchangeable, if you box it, you'd have to box a one, two, three, four, five, six and the reason it gets really expensive is it starts putting one, two, three, four, five, six for race two.
And, then one, two, three, four, five, six for race three.
So, you're basically paying one dollar for each of those bets in every single combination that there is and trust me there's a lot of them, especially with that many numbers, you're basically taking those six positions and writing out every single combination of those numbers in every single way.
And, that's basically a Daily Double.